const questions = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: 'What is the world’s largest land mammal?',
        answers: [{text: 'Elephant', correct: true}, {text: 'Giraffe', correct: false}, {text: 'Hippo', correct: false}]
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Rio de Janeiro is a city in which South American country?',
        answers: [{text: 'Brazil', correct: true}, {text: 'Equador', correct: false}, {text: 'Chile', correct: false}]
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which Middle Eastern city is also the name of a type of artichoke?',
        answers: [{text: 'Jerusalem', correct: true}, {text: 'Mecca', correct: false}, {text: 'Tunis', correct: false}]
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'With which sport is Silverstone most associated?',
        answers: [{text: 'Motor Racing', correct: true}, {
            text: 'Greyhound racing',
            correct: false
        }, {text: 'Horse racing', correct: false}]
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Nostradamus was famous for making what?',
        answers: [{text: 'Predictions', correct: true}, {
            text: 'Pies',
            correct: false
        }, {text: 'Hats for Queen Victoria', correct: false}]
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'In mythology, Romulus and Remus were brought up by which animal?',
        answers: [{text: 'Wolf', correct: true}, {text: 'Fox', correct: false}, {text: 'Cow', correct: false}]
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is the main source of vitamin C?',
        answers: [{text: 'Fruit', correct: true}, {text: 'Vegetables', correct: false}, {text: 'Beef', correct: false}]
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Insulin is commonly used to treat which condition?',
        answers: [{text: 'Diabetes', correct: true}, {text: 'Headache', correct: false}, {
            text: 'Vertigo',
            correct: false
        }]
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'The first atom bomb was dropped on which Japanese city?',
        answers: [{text: 'Hiroshima', correct: true}, {text: 'Nagasaki', correct: false}, {
            text: 'Tokyo',
            correct: false
        }]
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is dermatophobia the fear of?',
        answers: [{text: 'Skin disease', correct: true}, {text: 'Spiders', correct: false}, {
            text: 'Plants',
            correct: false
        }]
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'The Velocipede was a nineteenth-century prototype of what?',
        answers: [{text: 'A bicycle', correct: true}, {text: 'A boat', correct: false}, {
            text: 'An aeroplane',
            correct: false
        }],
    }
    // {
    //     id: 11,
    //     question: 'Which is Britain’s oldest Sunday newspaper, published for the first time in 1791?',
    //     answers: [{text: 'Observer', correct: true }, {text: 'Telegraph', correct: false}, {text: 'Daily Mail', correct: false}]
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 12,
    //     question: 'What was the middle name of Wolfgang Mozart?',
    //     answers: [{text: 'Amadeus', correct: true}, {text: 'Abraham', correct: false}, {text: 'Remus', correct: false}]
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 13,
    //     question: 'What is the art of stuffing animals for preservation?',
    //     answers: [{text: 'Taxidermy', correct: true}, {text: 'Meodermy', correct: false}, {text: 'Plastodermy', correct: false}]
    // },
    // {
    //     id: 14,
    //     question: 'The term bhp is used in auto industry, for what does it stand?',
    //     answers: [{text: 'Brake horse power', correct: true}, {text: 'Brake high power', correct: false}, {text: 'Blow hight power', correct: false}]
    // }
];

export default questions;
